This video is sponsored by Omniverse Connector.
Marvelous Designer 12.1 is now compatible with the USD file format and Omniverse Connector.
Click the copy button in the upper right corner of any window to open the Omniverse Connector window and the USD layer window.
Drag these windows to the right position.
Click the Create button in the window of the USD layer window to save the path and name to create an empty USD file.
The newly created file will automatically be set to authoring layer.usd.
Please note that you can create multiple USD layers,
but you can only change one of them.
If you want to edit the selected USD file under the authoring layer,
please select the 3D or 2D window of the USD file and then click the button in the upper right corner of any window to export it to the USD layer.
If there is no authoring layer at the moment,
please click the Create button in the window of the USD layer window to create a new one.
After setting up the PREM path, you can export the clothes.
According to the 3D clothing rendering style when exporting, the results will be different.
If the current 3D clothing rendering style is a thick texture surface,
then it will export the clothes with thickness.
If you want to export all the objects in the scene at the same time,
please go to the file in the main menu and export to USD.
When exporting the USD window, please select the object type you want to export.
At this time, you can choose to export thin or thick, and set the PREM path to complete the export.
You can import the import button in the window of the USD layer window to import the USD file,
or you can import the file in the main menu to import the USD file.
In the window of the USD layer window,
select the download type and object type.
If you want to import it as a virtual model,
you can choose to automatically create a test穿服.
Now the USD file has been successfully imported.
The grid and the material have appeared in the USD layer window,
and it is automatically exported to the main menu.
In the next step, you can import the 3D clothing rendering style.
The 3D clothing rendering style has been set to be an Authoring layer.
The 3D clothing rendering style is now set to Authoring layer.
If you would like to save the objects in the current scene
and add an extra block to the USD file,
please replace the plus option in the UD window.
Or, like in the video,
and enter the file in the menu to add a new layer of U.S.D.
Click the Clear button to clear all layers in the U.S.D. layer window
However, you can still find these objects in the 3D window
because they are the object of the scene
First, you need to connect to the Omniverse server
Please click the icon in the upper right corner of the Omniverse Connector window
and select Add Server in the drop-down menu
Enter the name of the server you want to connect to and click Add Server
As a reference, I entered localhost here
Please note that in order to use Omniverse Connector, Omniverse Create
you need to connect to the same server of Marvelous Designer
Open a U.S.D. file in Omniverse Create
Please note that in order to import text and objects at the same time
please make sure that the text folder and the U.S.D. folder are stored in the same path
In the Live menu in the upper right corner of the window, select Create Drawing
In the Live Session, click the name of the drawing in the window
A new drawing will be created
In Marvelous Designer, open the same U.S.D. file you opened in Omniverse Create
Now in Marvelous Designer, you can enter the drawing you created in Omniverse Create
Click the Omniverse Connector icon to enter the drawing
Select the name of the drawing created in Omniverse Create and click Add
After successfully entering the drawing
Go back to the U.S.D. layer window
A Live Session layer will appear
If another participant is adding your drawing
You can also click the refresh participant button to refresh participant information
When the Live Session layer set to Authoring is exported to the U.S.D. operation
You will see the file update in Omniverse Create
When the Live Session layer is set to Authoring
You can also click the refresh participant button to refresh participant information
However, when the normal U.S.D. layer set to Authoring is exported to the U.S.D. layer
These changes will not affect the objects in Omniverse Create
When the BaseUSD file is in the window
Click the Fetch button to synchronize the changes in Omniverse Create
If you need to leave the current drawing
Please open Omniverse Connect
And click on the Leave Drawing menu below
After clicking the Leave Drawing button, click the View